

Front-End Developer

📞 +905303001197 🔀 emir.mertoglu.97@gmail.com 🛚 in emirmertoglu

🔘 emirxmertoglu 💆 emirxmertoglu 🤘 emirxmertoglu.github.io

■ Profile

I have hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, JavaScript and .NET.

Building state-of-the-art, easy-to-use, user-friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine and I am confident I would be an excellent addition to the organization that I work for. In addition to my knowledge base, I actively seek out new technologies and stay up-to-date on industry trends and advancements.

Skills

React

Vue.Js

Node.Js

JavaScript

JSON

• HTML5

CSS3

.NET

ASP.NET

Flutter

C#

• (

Python

Firebase

• Git

Professional Experience

Gelecek Varlık FullStack Bootcamp Student,

11/2021 - 01/2022

Patika.dev ra

I've learned:

- .NET Core and React.
- N-Tier Architecture.
- · Restful API.

Front-End Developer Intern, Nutima Code 🗷

03/2021 - 10/2021

My role in Nutima:

- Coding modern and responsive websites.
- Making useful Vue.Js apps.

Projects

V-Book 7

A web app where you can view the top 100 classical books. I use Vue.Js & Vue Router & Json-Server with this project

COVID-19 Turkey Data 🗆

My goal in this project is to analyze the coronavirus data in the data set to make it meaningful and visualize it.

Kaggle link 🛮

Stuvent Mobile, for IEEEmadC | Mobile Application Development Contest My goal in this project is to announce the events that will take place at the university through the mobile application.

Organisations

GDG Mugla, Organizer and Developer □

09/2020 - 03/2021

When you join a Google Developer Group, you'll have the opportunity to meet local developers with similar interests in technology. A GDG meetup event includes talks on a wide range of technical topics where you can learn new skills through hands-on workshops. The community prides itself on being an inclusive environment where everyone and anyone interested in tech - from beginner developers to experienced professionals - all are welcome to join.

- I organized and helped with some events.
- I developed the GDG&WTM Mugla website.

DSC MSKU, Core Team Member 🗷

08/2019 - 08/2020

Developer Student Clubs are university-based community groups for students interested in Google developer technologies. By joining a DSC, students grow their knowledge in a peer-to-peer learning environment and build solutions for local businesses and their community.

• I organized and helped with some events.



Languages

English	Turkish
Professional working competence	Native

Education

Information Systems Engineering,	09/2018 – 06/2022
Mugla Sitki Kocman University	

GPA: +3.6/4

Management of Health Institutions, 09/2015 – 06/2018

Anadolu University

Paramedic, Nisantasi University 09/2015 – 06/2017



Computer Aided Advertising and Design

I can use most of Adobe Technologies: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, etc.

Cisco Networking Academy Mobility Fundamentals course, and demonstrating the ability to do following:

Wireless technologies, Wireless LAN standarts, Wireless LAN access point, router and client, Wireless LAN security, troubleshoot Wireless LANs

Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to Cybersecurity course, and demonstrating the ability to explain the following:

Global implications of cyber threats, Ways in which networks are vulnerable to attack, Impact of cyber-attacks on industries, Cisco's approach to threats detection and defense